<resources>
    <string name="app_name">xkcd phone</string>
    <string name="hw" translatable="false">Hello World!</string>
    <string name="hi">Hi!</string>
    <string name="kotlin">Kotlin is a cross-platform, statically typed, general-purpose programming language with type inference. Kotlin is designed to interoperate fully with Java, and the JVM version of its standard library depends on the Java Class Library, but type inference allows its syntax to be more concise. Kotlin mainly targets the JVM, but also compiles to JavaScript or native code (via LLVM). Language development costs are borne by JetBrains, while the Kotlin Foundation protects the Kotlin trademark.\n\nOn 7 May 2019, Google announced that the Kotlin programming language is now its preferred language for Android app developers. Since the release of Android Studio 3.0 in October 2017, Kotlin has been included as an alternative to the standard Java compiler. The Android Kotlin compiler lets the user choose between targeting Java 6 or Java 8 compatible bytecode. Kotlin fixes a series of issues that Java suffers from:\n\nNull references are controlled by the type system.\nNo raw types\nArrays in Kotlin are invariant\nKotlin has proper function types, as opposed to Java\'s SAM-conversions\nUse-site variance without wildcards\nKotlin does not have checked exceptions\n</string>
    <string name="xkcd_com_1363" translatable="false">xkcd.com/1363</string>
    <string name="service">Service has been launched. Click on the image! (Note: I am not responsible for any damage to your phone and recommend test-dropping it over your bed.) Now available in Chinese and Japanese!\n\nWARNING: You should probably use this app while alone. App plays audio.</string>
    <string name="wireless" translatable="false">Presented in partnership with Qualcomm, Craigslist, Whirlpool, Hostess, LifeStyles, and the US Chamber of Commerce. Manufactured on equipment which also processes peanuts. Price includes 2-year Knicks contract. Phone may extinguish nearby birthday candles. If phone ships with Siri, return immediately; do not speak to her and ignore any instructions she gives. Do not remove lead casing. Phone may attract/trap insects; this is normal. Volume adjustable (requires root). If you experience sudden tingling, nausea, or vomiting, perform a factory reset immediately. Do not submerge in water; phone will drown. Exterior may be frictionless. Prolonged use can cause mood swings, short-term memory loss, and seizures. Avert eyes while replacing battery. Under certain circumstances, wireless transmitter may control God.</string>
</resources>
